Оглашавајте свој производ или марку код нас; контактирајте www.OpenSubtitles.org
www.titlovi.com
Jack, Jack.
Everbody, listen up.
We got a report people trapped
on the 12th floor above.
lt's going to explode at anytime.
Everybody keep together,
maintain radio contact.
Why is it always have
to be the 12th floor?
Why can't it be on the 4th?
Let's move it, Grandpa.
Come on.
Ladder 49,
on the 12th floor
Commencing search.
Lenny, take Jack.
All right, Capt.
Come on, Jack.
Anybody here?
Hello.
Fire department.
Hey, Jack.
He's over here.
We found one of them. He's alive.
We're bringing him out.
Jack, get his hand.
Copy that. We got one too.
We meet you at the stairwell.
- Take a breath out of my mask.
- l got him. l got him.
We're bringing him down the stairs now
- Where's Phil?
They said there were 2 of them.
They said there were only 2.
On this level.
On this floor. Over there.
- l'm gonna go look for him.
- Maintain radio contact.
Looking for alternative. Still
searching for victims on level 12th.
Ladder 49.
1 to 3, we copy that.
Can you stand?
Come on, let's go.
Ladder 49.
Portable 1 to 3, are you all right?
Yeah, l got another one.
Portable 3 in command.
Command, do you copy?
Copy that.
We're re-positioning Truck 51 .
Nice and easy.
Truck 51 to Ladder 49
Bring him down, Jack.
Bring him down.
- What's your name, Phil?
- Yeah, Phil.
Here, Phil. Can you hold this?
Can you hold this against your face?
Listen to me, l'm gonna
tie you up right now, all right?
Nice and easy.
Portable 3 in command.
...the victim down.
All right, so now listen to me.
Take this off. Listen to me.
Trust me, keep your eyes on me, okay?
You keep your eyes on me, l got you.
Trust me.
You look at me. You look at me.
Stay right there.
l can't do this.
l am right here. You can do it, Phil.
- l can't do this.
Yes, you can. l am gonna help you.
l got guys on the ground.
Trust me, Phil. Trust me.
l can't.
You have to go. l'm not leaving
until you leave and you do it, Phil.
l promise l got you.
You just look right here.
You got 30 Feet, Jack.
Stay right here.
You got 15 Feet.
Bring him down. Bring him down.
Hey, you're a rookie?
Drop your bag. Take the staircase.
Captain's office.
- You're the rookie, right?
- Yeah.
Fire fighter Jack Morrison
reporting, sir.
Your shift start at 7:00, son.
Save it. Sit down.
Let me tell you something, boy.
Engine 33 is the busiest and most
discipline firehouse in the city.
No room for slackers.
You got that?
l know that, sir.
Get over 4, 000 calls a year.
A lot of action. You've to be
willing to go the extra mile.
Are you, Jack? Are you willing
to go the extra mile?
- Yes, sir.
- l don't think so.
Sorry, Capt.
Father Hogan is here.
Welcome to Engine 33.
Good to have you onboard, son.
- Ray, how are you?
- Jack Morrison.
He's a great guy.
- Are you Catholic?
- Yeah.
Most of the guys are.
Priest comes around twice a year.
We all go to confession.
...you find God.
Bless me Father for l have sin.
7 years since my last confession.
7 years is a long time.
Robbery, fraud, taxes?
Taxes, always taxes.
How about sex?
Quite a bit.
- Are you married?
- No.
- Are you a virgin?
- No, Father.
Wait a minute,
No, you wait a minute.
- Dennis Gauquin.
- My older uglier brother.
You put one foot in here,
this dog will tear your ass off.
What the hell is this?
Are you stupid?
- There's no paper.
- lt's right there.
lt's not on the hole.
Who ask your opinion?
About 3 more blocks.
North Avenue.
Pull out of the way, asshole.
How you feeling, kid?
Your first fire,
you ready to break your 'cherry'?
That one.
Go, go, go, go.
Your helmet.
Slow down.
- Charge the light.
- Charge.
Slow down, slow down.
Keep going.
They're just rat.
Come on, let's go.
You ready?
Moving in.
Now, now.
That's it.
Hit it high, hit it high.
You did it, man.
Good job.
Get me up the speed.
We got a 20th storey building.
Most of it concrete.
Most of the fire on the top 8th floor.
And after the explosion on the 12th,
one of our guy,
Jack Morrison, Ladder 49.
- Any radio contact with him?
- None.
Anybody with him?
The other members of
Ladder 49 make it out.
He is in the stairwell
with the victim.
Deputy Chief Communication, l'm
on location assuming command.
Strike out a 4th alarm.
Okay, shut down all
exterior operations.
Get your asses in there and find him.
Go, go, go.
Commander Ladder 49.
Jack, come in.
Ladder 49, Morrison
Jack, it's Kennedy.
How are you holding up?
Do you know where you are?
No, l was on 12th
How you doing in there?
Okay, hold tight. We got units
coming in after you.
You make it. lt's going to be okay.
You did a greatjob.
Jack, switch to different channel.
Try 8.
Switch to different channel.
Trapped in here like some dumb rookie.
What do you expect?
l did the best l could
l told you. Didn't l tell you?
Hey, we need ketchup.
l am going in.
Excuse me.
- Can l ask you a question?
- Sure.
- Who are this for?
- For us.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- You can't eat this.
- Why not?
These are for lonely girls who stay
at home at night watching TV.
Lieutenant, right?
Lieutenant Jack Morrison.
l am Captain Dennis Gauquin.
You ever heard of that?
- No.
- Best seafood in town.
Do you know where the ketchup is?
But l did have a goose.
A goose in my locker.
Hey, hold up.
- l hear a lot about you.
- Yeah?
Oh my God, what was that?
Last one to empty their glasses
run naked around the bar.
All right, loser takes off
all their clothes.
l said last to empty their glasses.
Did l say anything about drinking?
The lady is right, Tommy.
Please kill me.
Jack.
Ladder 49,
We have structure collapse inside.
There's no way around it.
l don't care what your problem is.
Just keep going.
We're going to need
some equipment up here.
We're on Site 2.
Waiting instruction, over.
Lenny, Lenny.
How are we going to
get through all this?
What do you need?
- We need that equipment over here.
- You got it.
Come on, we got to tore this up.
May the Lord bless you.
Happy years together
So you may enjoy the
rewards of a good life.
And after you've loyally served
this kingdom on earth,
Then we welcome you
into kingdom in Heaven.
Bless you in the name of
Father and of the Son
And of the Holy Spirit.
You may now kiss the bride.
l now present Mr and
Mrs Jack Morrison.
Your husband is an
excellent fire fighter.
Look after him for me, will you?
- l'll help him look after himself.
- Even better.
All right, this next song goes out to
our newly-wed by special request.
Jack, get up here.
Sit down, join the club.
They are quite a choir, huh.
- Captain Kennedy?
- You're the rookie?
- You Catholic?
- Yeah.
- Are you a virgin?
- No, Father.
lf you want to have sex,
you should get married.
- l can't.
- Why?
- lt's not allowed.
- What do you mean it's not allowed?
Excuse me?
l am gay.
- Here we go.
- l am good.
l am good. l am not drinking.
You can have it.
lt's okay. l'm not going to drink.
l'm just going to grab a Coke.
What, are you pregnant?
l was going to tell you later tonight.
l want to suprise you.
No more drinks for Linda.
Double for Jack.
He's going to be a father.
- Keep the money.
- Save it for the baby.
Jack, you can't have a baby
without a shower.
- l'm getting too old for this shit.
- You got that right.
This is bullshit, man.
Let it burn.
Tommy, get the door!
Evacuate now, evacuate now.
Activate the alarm.
lt's no good.
You guys take as much
time off as you need.
He wasn't paying attention.
Just shut up and wash the dishes,
rookie.
What the hell is going on here?
l come back from telling a mother
that her son is dead.
And this is going on in my house,
in my house.
We deal with this
by sticking together.
We take it. We learn from it.
And we get back to the god damn truck
and that's how we honor Dennis.
You got that?
Do it.
Don't you think it might fall apart?
l hope not.
l'm thinking about changing job.
What do you mean?
Does that mean you will
be taking Dennis's place?
Would you?
Capt, this stuff is great.
That's my grandfather.
This is his helmet.
These are my dad's.
That's him.
He got after he past away.
- lt's medal of honor.
- Yeah.
So, what's going on?
Something l want to talk to you about.
l was thinking about
transferring to Truck.
Why do you want to do that for?
Truck is a whole different thing.
You get lost in the smoke.
lt's not a good idea.
- l love being on the pipes. lt's just
- Just what?
lt's what l want, Mike.
But you got to tell me something,
if this isn't for you,
You tell me right away.
You promise?
Yes, sir.
We're coming to get you.
Hey, Lenny. Grab the rope.
- Try not to look down, Jack.
- Thanks, Lenny.
All right, Tommy. Let it down.
We got you, Jack. You're good.
We're on the scene in Chopper 7.
We got a burning building in
downtown on Culbert Street.
A lot of flame, a lot of smoke.
Stop, stop.
Your eyes start to burn and
the heat from the flames,
Just wait, just wait.
There they go.
Close your eyes.
Put your head against me.
You would be okay.
You just stay calm, okay?
He shattered the glass.
They're inside now. We're
going to try get this guy's name.
Let's get in closer, Jerry.
Get in closer for a look.
What's the matter?
l saw you on the news, Jack.
Linda, what's wrong?
Dangling from a rope.
How can you tell me that
it is not dangerous?
When we talk about it, l asked you
and you said it wasn't dangerous.
l said it wasn't anymore dangerous
than being on Engine.
l never said it wasn't dangerous.
Did you see me right now? Do you?
'Coz it isn'tjust about us.
Have you thought about that?
l am scare. l can't sleep.
l keep having that dream, about the
in front of the house
When you don't come home.
l understand. Jack, listen up.
Can you identify anything around you?
There's door to my left.
The best guess is he's right
about here in this area,
We break through this wall,
get us into the Control Room.
Okay, now look, Jack,
this is very important.
Right behind you is a wall. Behind
that wall is the Control Room.
lf we can break through the wall,
we can buy some time.
Can you do that?
Give it a shot.
l need 2 man upstair
Ladder 1 7
Got to make a wish first.
l wish for a Barbie.
You're not suppose to say it loud.
But will l get it now?
Sorry, l am late.
This is for the Birthday girl.
Happy Birthday.
Sitting here at night
watching the romantic light
Beauty and the Beast,
it is hell of a book.
lt's good. l never read it before.
Have you consider
baby-sitting full time?
Shouldn't you left by now?
Yeah, l can't find my key.
Do you see them?
Yeah, they're by the door
where you left them.
Can we take
to the game on Saturday?
Game on Saturday?
Yeah, definitely
What is it?
lt's a tree.
Tommy, check out downstairs.
Okay, let's go.
Come on, come on.
Captain, let's find Tommy
and get the hell out of here.
Over here.
- You find anyone?
- No, nobody.
Get the hell out of here.
Come on, let's go, let's go.
We're putting you on a chopper
and take you to Gilford.
What's wrong?
You okay?
Come on, Nicky. Get upstairs
and brush your teeth.
What's going on?
Who told you?
Yeah, steam can burn your skin.
New skin grows back
Tommy's face got burn but
his skin will grow back.
ls it hurt?
Yeah, when it happens.
Well, we're trained not to get hurt.
Long before you was borned,
l was trained.
Sometimes, things can go wrong.
We're not afraid 'coz
we do it to save people.
lf things do go wrong,
l got your Uncle Mike
All my friends at firehouse, you know
they never let anything happen to me.
Can you do me a favor?
You tell Julie Costa that Alex's dad
got burnt trying to save people.
He's going to be okay.
You're not going to go in?
l come back another time.
No, it's fine. You can go in now.
Doctor said l am going to make it.
Of course she want to bring the kid.
They want to see you.
l am scare, Jack.
l was the hero.
Don't say that.
How does he look?
He's in lot of pain?
l'll like to go see him.
Because he's our friend.
Do what you want.
Are you telling me
you don't want me to go?
- No, l don't want you to go.
- Why?
'Coz you're going to see him
and you're going to freak out
There's more for you to worry about.
More for me to worry about or
more for you to worry about, Jack?
Don't tell me you don't worry.
Are you trying to pick a fight?
Big office, secretary,
so much paper work
What's eating you?
Who is this?
And that is definitely not her.
Yeah, maybe l've to come
slide down your chimney tonight.
- What's wrong with you?
- Nothing.
We got to talk.
Anything else?
Do you still love the job
like you used to?
You've been through a lot.
What can l say?
You lost your best friend
How are Linda and the kids?
When l was married, my wife
hated me being a fire fighter
You're different,
you're a good father.
You're worried but you should worried.
You know, maybe the time for a change
l was thinking there's
this job at headquarters
You should ask yourself that question.
You go home, talk to Linda.
You know, be honest to yourself.
Nothing wrong with moving on.
So, what did he say?
What is that mean?
...increase in pay.
ls that what you want?
You know, the kids are scare.
You upset
So, this is about me and
the kids again, isn't it?
We married 10 years.
And l do get scare.
But l deal with it.
lf l still love the job the way l did,
From midnight to the current hour,
Lenny, Lenny
l got it, l got it. Go.
Where's your mom and dad?
- Shopping.
- They leave you alone?
- l was with Jenny.
- Who is Jenny?
My cousin. She was baby-sitting.
Where do you live?
Where is your apartment? Show me.
Hello?
Hello? Fire department.
Anybody here? Fire department.
l got something.
You're bleeding.
Let's get you treated.
Your shift is over.
All units report to the
now.
Jack, come in, Jack.
The condition deteriorated rapidly.
Ladder 49, there's a Control Room
straight ahead. Jack is in there.
Keep going, just keep going.
Command, stand by.
l see a door, l see a door.
Jack, they're getting close. You just
hang on there, Jack. Just hang on.
Jack, hold on. We're right here.
Jack, talk to me.
Listen to me.
Mike, tell Linda l love her.
- Do you hear me?
- Yeah, l heard you.
You tell them that, you hear me?
l will.
All units, evacuate the
building immediately.
lt's never an easy thing saying goodbye
to your brother fire-fighter.
And this time, particularly it's
difficult for me because l watch Jack
Grew into well, into one of the
finest fire-fighter l've ever known.
He join this department because
he want to help people.
Who knows how many homes are still
standing because Jack was there.
How many life were spared?
He gives his life for that cause.
We'll never forget you, Jack.
And we're better for having you.
l make you this 1 promise,
Tomorrow, when the bell rings,
we'll be back on the truck.
Because you're the
bravest of the brave.
People always asking me how the
fire-fighter run into burning building
When everyone else is running out?
Jack, you answer that question
by saving another man's life.
Your courage is the answer.
And today we will be as brave as you,
By not mourning you
but celebrating your life.
Preuzeto sa www.titlovi.com
Молимо вас да оцените овај титл на www.osdb.link/83jcc
Помозите другим корисницима да изаберу најбоље титлове