-== [ www.OpenSubtitles.org ] ==-
CJ Entertainment presents
Moho Film production
PARK Chan-wook film
Executive Producer/Miky LEE
Associate Producers/
KIM Joo-sung, Joon H. CHOI
Executive Producer/LEE Tae-hun
Casting by LEE Joo-yeol,
PARK Sung-hea, CHO Hae-sung
Line Producer/KANG Hyun
Assistant Director/SEOK Min-woo
Makeup Artist/KIM Hyun-jung
Sound Recordist/JUNG Jin-uk
Sound Design/KIM Suk-won,
KIM Chang-sub
LIM Soo-jung, JUNG Ji-Hoon
One, connect the speakers
And assemble the covers
with care to direction.
speaker...
Covers, direction...
Two, turn the routers to the end
in the direction of the stator
Fit the knobs in a straight line
Music/CHO Young-uk
with the screws.
Routers...
Direction to stator.
Costume Design/CHO Sang-kyung
Young-goon before the incident?
For instance, did she stop
eating suddenly?
I'm afraid I didn't have time
to notice things like that
Visual Effects/LEE Zeon-hyoung
I'm so busy at the restaurant.
Truth is, my mother
was raised by Young-goon.
Pardon me?
No, I mean, my mother
raised Young-goon.
- That's why the young one talks
- Three, push metal plate 2 x 23 in...
- rather like an old person.
- and set it on the back case
Editors/KIM Sang-bum, KIM Jae-bum
Could I meet her grandmother?
She went to a home for Alzheimer's.
She ate nothing but radish
for six months.
- Radish?
- Like for pickled radishes.
- Bolt 1.7 x 4
- I see.
Yes?
70kg of tripe, did you get
the head meat, ears, liver, and womb?
No, we need to get at least 100kg.
You know it's hard to get nowadays.
When I was young,
Once when I was little, I came home
early from school with a bad headache.
- A head?
- Yeah, head meat.
No, get 60kg of tongue.
Yeah.
It hurt so much that
as soon as I got home...
I started calling from the yard!
Mom!
Five, fasten the insulator to
the speaker on the front case...
Insulator, speaker, front case,
assemble the circuit board...
- What are you doing?
- Back case...
Volume...
Bolts 2 x 8, fasten...
She was...
Feeding some mice.
Six,
Connect the tester and
switch on the radio.
Switch of radio.
Lighting/PARK Hyun-won
to the home for eating radishes, too?
The smell was really bad
whenever she ate radishes.
10 to 25...
- Were they pet mice?
- Normal.
They were strangers to me.
- Seven, once the check is done...
- The check.
- Pull the antenna up high...
- The Antenna.
Turn the frequency knob to find
a broadcast station.
Broadcast, broadcast.
Eight, split the end of the wire
in two and take of the covering
My mother told me.
She had a secret that
she really shouldn't tell.
But she didn't want
to hide it anymore
That those mice were
my little brothers and sisters.
'As much as you're my daughter,
so are these mice'
'I am the mother mouse.'
Production design/RYU Seong-hie
- I see.
- Nine
- Cut left wrist with knife...
- Wrist... knife...
My poor mother.
Mother was always so timid...
- Put in the uncovered wires...
- Wires...
Did Young-goon know about
her grandmother's story, too?
Bind it with duct tape.
- Young-goon?
- Tape.
Of course not.
Mother probably felt a little
closer to the mice that day.
Cinematography/CHUNG Chung-hoon
to the pig intestines, too.
Written by CHUNG Seo-kyung
with your patients?
PARK Chan-Wook
Ten, plug into an outlet.
Plug.
Did Young-goon ever say
Producer/LEE Chun-young
she was something else, too?
Never, doctor.
Young-goon is a human being.
Her grandmother's thing
wouldn't have much to do...
with Young-goon's trying
to commit suicide, would it?
I'm a Cyborg, but that's OK
My girl will be okay, right?
Produced and Directed by
PARK Chan-wook
SON Eun-young, WANG Gob-dan
CHA Young-goon
I wonder if a kid like you
could take the food here.
What could your parents
be thinking of, sending you here?
After all, parents are always
the most important factor.
For girls,
it's especially the father.
Like for her over there.
They say 10 years ago,
a patient disappeared.
His name was Oh Dong-soo and
he was thin and pale like rice paper.
And he was plagued
by non-stop hiccups.
The staff, the military and police,
they searched everywhere for him
They even had the hounds up
in the mountains.
Said he was a dangerous psychopath.
About a week went by...
before they realized this clock
was making hiccupping sounds
He was comfortably
curled up in here, dead.
Listen.
That sound.
I can't live
like this anymore.
Come over here.
Look at here.
Believe it or not, kid.
This is crazy!
- Listen everyone, this is insane!
- Dae-pyong, calm down!
Who put you up to this?
You thieving bastards!
How dare you imprison a police
officer on duty! Bastards!
- Catch Park Il-soon!
- Calm down! Dae-pyong, please!
- Calm down!
- Police!
911!
Dr. Kim!
He did it again.
A police officer?
Who is he kidding?
He's just a uniform freak.
He put on a schoolgirl uniform,
killed his wife...
And burned his house down.
Let's change the subject.
That guy in the mask, they say
he used to be really handsome.
But after he was gang raped
in the army, he went mad.
He blamed his handsome face and
burned it with cigarette butts.
Then he sewed up his own anus.
That man over there.
He's a farmer from Kyung-san.
A nice, quiet bachelor all his life,
good to everyone in the village.
But he fell in love with a calf
that he delivered himself.
Its name was Jenny, I think.
He brought it into his room to live
It couldn't talk, didn't have hands,
but he would wash its face.
And listened to the radio with it,
and so on.
The town folk thought he was a freak
and had him put in here.
But he really only loved
Jenny platonically.
I'm depressed.
Who's this chick?
Huh?
I don't know.
Sul-mi! You're not supposed to
take a patient around like this.
Not my fault.
Someone left her with me.
Don't be that way with me, doctor!
You know I'm sick! You shouldn't
embarrass me like this.
Did she tell you many stories,
Young-goon?
The things she tells you...
That's right! They're all lies!
Yes, they're all lies.
It's called mythomania.
She has an illness that makes her
tell tall tales.
She loses all her memory each time
she gets shock therapy
So she makes up stories to
take the place of her memories.
What's wrong?
She won't talk.
Psychotic depression?
Her grandmother was schizophrenic.
Thought she was a mouse.
Was she afraid of her mother-in-law?
How'd you know that?
I once saw...
Two patients who thought
they were mice.
They both said they were afraid
of their mothers-in-law.
I don't know where to start with her.
She won't stir a finger.
Her eyes are out of focus.
Hey kids!
I'm here. You fluorescent lights.
No use pretending
you don't understand me.
Lights here aren't very friendly,
are they?
No matter how tired you are,
it's bad manners not to say hello.
How are you,
after working all day?
Really?
Then...
Perhaps some adlay tea, please?
Thank you kindly.
Maybe the lights in the wards
will be friendlier.
Since they rest at night.
So you knew from the beginning
that you're a light?
I only found out later in life
that I'm a cyborg.
The white 'uns came and took
my granny away in an ambulance.
You know the white 'uns!
They're all over the place here.
They wear white-doctors, nurses...
Granny!
Right, and orderlies!
- She took the radish.
- Granny!
But left her dentures.
So I ran after her with them.
Granny needs them to eat radish.
She's a mouse, you know.
Just then, a bike came up
and took me.
But a bike can't beat an ambulance.
Even a kid in knickers knows that.
So I bawled and you know
what the bike said?
'A cyborg can beat anything.'
'How come you don't know that
when you're a cyborg yourself?'
So I had to pretend
I had always known.
But the problem was I couldn't
catch up to the ambulance for real.
So, ask me what I said
to the bike then.
'Confounded fool,
I'm all out of battery, you moron.'
So I endeavored to recharge
by listening
to educational broadcasts
at the factory.
I'm only fully recharged
when it lights up to here.
But look, I'm almost on empty.
I did as the broadcast told me,
and the ambulance brought me here.
I'm a machine, but...
I didn't come with an instruction
manual or a label on me anywhere.
I still don't know what my purpose is.
What was I made for?
You didn't eat your lunch, did you?
You won't be able to starve
yourself to death that way.
The cafeteria ladies keep tabs
on everything you eat.
A girl like you once tried
to starve herself to death.
She was so enthusiastic.
But hospitals have
force-feeding machines.
Doctors and professors meet
to confer on how to feed you...
It's embarrassing to have them force
food up your nose in front of people.
So that girl is still eating,
and alive and kicking.
Sad, isn't it?
So I was thinking...
Want me to help you?
Broadcast, broadcast!
Broadcast!
Listen. There are some
really good messages.
Time for meditation.
Get up and listen to the hum of
the fridge in the middle of night
On a cold winter morning.
Feel the sound of the boiler
that has been running all night
They move us to tears because
they have a purpose of existence.
Think of the lighthouse's holy
and beautiful heart of love.
To be continued.
If only I had just one
purpose of existence, too.
Il-soon, please, your mask!
Will the pretty Gop-dahn
please explain?
Our hospital has stabilizing rooms...
for those who cause discomfort
to others or create safety issues.
And when it is deemed
a necessary treatment...
- With the patient's consent.
- What consent?
You told me to stay in
the stabilizing
room until I gave my consent!
I told you before that if you hit
others for no reason like that...
You have to go in the stabilizing room.
But Il-soon is a thief!
A detestable and shameless psycho,
anti-social and schizophrenic!
Isn't that an attack
on his character?
It's not an attack!
It's defense!
He stole something
very important to me!
Alright, what did Il-soon steal
from you, Dae-pyong?
They all point to me
if anything goes missing.
For the past 3 days, I can't
even receive a simple serve.
While Park Il-soon won 5 games
just yesterday!
With the unique service technique
that I developed 12 years ago!
There's no point not stealing.
They all think I did it anyway.
Come on, that's not true.
...12 years ago!
I see, you lost your ping-pong game.
It was about a month ago.
I suddenly lost my appetite
and couldn't eat.
Think of what it did to my skin!
Il-soon came and ate all my food.
He's the one who stole the elastic
band around my waist
for a whole week.
The elastic band
for your pajamas?
No, this skin colored elastic band
I was born with around my waist!
Look at this.
It's all stretched out!
Does he mean he was born
wearing pajamas?
Then is Il-soon the one who stole
my memory, too?
You bastard!
You thief!
- Give me back my ping-pong!
- You stretched my band!
Mr. Pajamas, please!
I told you your mother
didn't leave because of you.
Yeah, right!
Then how come she never
called but once?
To tell me not to forget to
brush my teeth before bed!
Fine! I'll admit it!
Last night, I stole Thursday.
Whose Thursday?
How can a person steal Thursday?
Look, Thursday's panties are missing.
Monday's are right here, where else?
I had no idea.
He's really good.
This is a fortuitous crossing of
paths, for sure.
I must find out more about this thief.
I have this thing
I want someone
to steal away from me.
I don't know how I'll ever thank you.
So sorry for being so slow!
Hello, everyone!
How are you?
- Have you had lunch?
- Sure.
Yeah, I have.
Have you had lunch?
Don't skip the meal.
Psycho.
I'm not a psy-cho.
I'm a cy-borg.
Ah, I let slip.
I promised Mom I wouldn't.
Mom, I think I'm a cyborg.
What's that?
I think it's kind of like a robot?
Have you missed a period?
Because you're a cybor?
Anything you want to eat?
Like radishes?
Then it's okay.
Now go get some sleep.
It's okay if you're a cybor.
It won't interfere with
the way you live.
Just don't let anybody know.
Who would come to eat at a shop
where the daughter's a cybor?
Cyborg, are you thinking of
your Granny?
I certainly am.
You aren't feeling sad, are you?
No, why of course not!
She's wondering about you, too...
And why you haven't killed
the white 'uns yet.
She wonders why you don't bag
the white 'uns that dragged her away.
And bring her the dentures.
But I...
I don't have enough power.
This charging method seems to
have its limitations.
I hope it's not
because of sympathy.
You know that sympathy is
the worst of the 7 Deadly Sins.
No, really...
It's not because of sympathy.
For your reference,
the other 6 are as follows.
Being sad.
Restlessness.
Hesitating about anything.
Useless daydreaming.
Feeling guilty.
Thankfulness.
The above was in
the order of evilness.
Yes
Useless daydreaming about whether
the white 'uns have grannies, too...
Sympathy for their grannies
if the white 'uns died...
And hesitating about killing them.
You must forego these sins.
Floriculture Therapy
Take your ping-pong back.
It makes my butt itchy
every time I play.
The right cheek.
Transfer!
- Go Dae-pyong!
- Go, doc!
He is very polite.
He's so humble he can't
even walk forwards.
Court etiquette, he says.
He thinks it's his fault
when anything goes wrong.
Are you there?
- Hello?
- What is it?!
Just wondering if it was
my fault you lost?
He happened to drive past
the scene of an accident...
And he was convinced
it was his fault.
He followed the victims around
apologizing.
When they couldn't stand it
any longer...
They reported him and
he was brought to this hospital.
I said no!
It wasn't your fault, Duk-chun.
It's my ping-pong!
It's too itchy to play!
Duk-chun is an expert at saying
redundant things.
Isn't ping-pong about
giving and receiving?
I don't think so!
Must one always receive
after giving?
Can't there be ping-pong
where we only give?
So it was my fault.
A cat is, above all,
a furry animal.
Actually, my wife is furry, too.
Isn't it obvious I'd become impotent
with a furry wife?
I'll hear from the judiciary soon.
I filed a suit against her.
She hid that she's a furry monster
when we got married.
Making a police officer impotent is
an obstruction of his duties.
Alright, transfer!
Hello, there!
How are you all doing?
Have you had lunch?
Hello!
How are you? Hello!
Have you had lunch?
Oh my god.
I'm so sorry.
Are you okay?
- How can I tell you how sorry I am?
- I'm so tired!
I'm sorry I made you tired.
Why do I always tire people out
like this? I'm sorry.
I had a dream...
To make amends to everyone
I've ever troubled.
People should make amends
whenever they've caused trouble.
But now...
I've had all my politeness stolen.
Now how am I supposed to apologize?
Do you remember
where you lost it?
You people don't know what
it's like to have troubled others!
You bitch!
Please steal it.
My sympathy.
Like Thursday.
Sympathy?
What's that?
The feeling that stops me
from killing those I should.
I keep thinking...
What if I killed the white 'uns...
And they have grannies, too?
The poor grannies...
Look, miss.
When you speak to a person,
You have to speak so that
the person can understand.
Well, sympathy is...
My mom, aunt and uncle
shouldn't have acted that way!
How could they have
so little sympathy?
No one's a mouse because
they want to be a mouse.
Don't even talk about moms!
I'm sorry.
And if you keep asking me
to steal something...
That's not stealing. It's just
taking what you're giving.
Then what should I do?
Well, when I...
When I set out to steal
something from someone...
I have to watch that person
stealthily for a few days.
Can you do that?
No problem.
I have to watch them stealthily
and find something I want to steal
Then I get the stealthy
desire to steal.
Are you really up to this?
You can trust me.
Once I have the stealthy
desire to steal...
It can only be completed if I steal
without the person's consent.
They have to hate
my stealing from them.
Can you do that for me?
promise to hate it.
I beg of you to do it.
Since I walk backwards
she can't follow me...
So she spends her time
talking to machines
with those dentures in.
She holds her hand out to doctors
and nurses to shake hands...
And she wants to very much
but then suddenly pulls away.
She loathes it so much
her hands tremble.
Why does she hold out her hand if
she dislikes shaking hands so much?
She hasn't done much,
why is she so exhausted?
Because she doesn't eat, no wonder.
Coffee.
Black.
Are you over your flickering now?
Lights, vending machine,
public phone, hiccup clock!
Have you seen my granny's dentures?
You can't understand me
without the dentures, can you?
Where are those dentures?
Young-goon doesn't eat her food.
Gop-dahn eats it.
P.S. Gop-dahn eats it.
For today's gathering,
we're talking about
our most painful partings.
How about you Duk-chun?
Ready...
My most painful parting was?
Mother...
fucker!
How about me, doctor?
Sure! Ready?
My most painful parting was?
When I was 15 and my mom left home...
She took the entire family set
of electrical toothbrushes...
And left for good.
After that, I became a thief.
You damned thief!
Take your politeness back, mister.
Your walking backwards and
saying redundant things, all of it.
But why? I don't want to.
People can't follow me from behind!
Here. Transfer!
This news just in.
She was moved to a nearby hospital
but never woke from her coma
Granny is... critical?
In critical condition...
The white 'uns...
Granny... earring...
Oh... eating... radish...
They don't like it.
So...
They won't let me give
her the dentures.
My Granny... loves...
radish... so much...
I must... kill them... all.
Confounded bastards...
Please...
Steal...
My sympathy!
Stop crying!
Do you hate it?
No?
I told you that you must hate it!
I hate it! I hate it! I hate it!
I truly hate it!
I'm taking away your sympathy.
Alright, transfer!
When I count to five and
snap my fingers, open your eyes.
One, two, three, four.
Five.
No sympathy.
Young-goon!
Young-goon?
My battery...
Battery is...
Empty.
Young-goon!
Young-goon?
Wang Gop-dahn!
Gop-dahn!
Tell me the truth
Did you really eat
Young-goon's food?
Beautiful Berne.
Where the clear stream flows.
How much more will
I have to practice...
to get into the Edelweiss
Boys' and Girls' Choir?
In my case, I have an elastic band
around my waist
I always feel reassured
even in strange places.
Stop, or our eyes will meet
and it will be scandalous.
Red alpine roses.
Blooming in the dew.
When my life reaches its end.
The elastic band will be
stretched to its limit
I've already been practicing for
31 years since I failed the audition.
Snap! And I'll just go back...
To where I started off originally.
Das Obuh-lan-ya Obuh-lan.
The beautiful mountains of Berne.
Das Obuh-lan-ya Obuh-lan,
Oh, my love Berne...
Do you think humans can
go against gravity?
Do you think...
humans can go...
against gravity?
I succeeded in my experiment!
Sleep flying!
Peppermint sherbet and
persimmon socks
They create static electrical tension.
And that makes the body float.
Like superconducting
magnetically levitated trains.
Watch. Here I go.
Should avoid eating things like
chicken right before flying.
Young-goon's always lying down
so I can't see her much these days
Can you see me, Sul-mi?
Partially, but...
Why don't you take it off?
What if I do and I'm invisible?
My mom and dad used to act like
I wasn't there,
even when I was.
That's why I'm good at stealing.
Because people can't see
me sometimes.
From the time I was 20,
I learned electrical wiring.
I made good money,
but I got caught stealing a motorcycle.
When I was being tried, the judge
said something only I could hear
Defendant Park Il-soon
will eventually vanish into a dot.
You shithead!
Oh dear!
I did all kinds of things in jail
Because I felt like I was vanishing.
I stole other people's
clothes to wear
And I brushed my teeth diligently.
Once your teeth start to go,
there's no turning back.
That's true.
I had a psych evaluation and...
They said I'm schizophrenic
and anti-social.
Anti-social?
Like stealing and fighting
for no reason.
And not having any sense of
guilt or sympathy.
But I don't know why
they call me anti-social.
I have my reasons for stealing.
I'm afraid I'll vanish.
I'm anti-vanishing.
They say there's no cure
for being anti-social.
But the doctor says to have hope.
Sometimes it goes away on its own
30 or 40 years later.
Though usually that 30-40 years
are spent in prison...
I see.
I admit myself here because
I don't want to go to prison.
Taxi!
When I feel it coming on,
I head straight back here.
This is my fifth hospitalization
in four years.
With steady labor, I can manage
the hospital and medication costs.
But do you think I can hold out
for 40 years like this?
Without vanishing into a dot?
What do you think?
Just...
Give up hope.
And...
Keep your strength up!
Strength?
But Young-goon has no strength!
I never thought you'd open up
about yourself like that.
Well, you're getting
shock therapy today.
Sul-mi?
People tend to think
that shock therapy is inhumane
But it isn't really, ma'am.
It's a widely used treatment for
depression or catatonia.
I see.
There are patients who don't eat.
Because of auditory hallucinations,
delusions, or emotional distress.
They usually start eating again
after 2-3 days
when medicated.
But Young-goon has such
serious side effects to medication.
Young-goon doesn't eat,
sleep, or move.
She throws up her medication.
She's completely catatonic.
Are there side effects
to shock therapy?
There can be some memory loss.
That loss is okay,
but please just make her eat again.
You get here?
I should be getting merciless
as soon as possible...
Since I'm the only one
you've got, Granny.
Just wait.
I'll get you your dentures
And kill them all.
What?
The purpose of...
Of existence is...
Slowly.
Granny.
What?
Charging complete!
Are you okay?
Yes.
Who am I?
Dr. Choi Seul-ki
Who's the president of Korea?
It's okay. It'll come to you.
That kind of memory skips back soon.
I never knew in the first place.
What do you remember?
Everything.
It was quiet and I was hooked up
with wires all over me.
What else?
In the incubator.
My granny told me.
She said I was weak from birth
They were afraid I'd die so
I was in an incubator for a while
Electrical wires came all around
and raised me.
Young-goon.
Can you tell me why you won't eat?
Do you hear voices
telling you not to eat?
Are you worried the food
is poisoned?
Do you want to starve
yourself to death?
It's okay
I sometimes
feel like dying, too.
Why would a young lady
like you want to die?
We must carry on living
through thick and thin.
I can walk from here.
I can feel my strength coming back.
I feel like I've been born again.
No hesitating about anything.
No feeling guilty.
'I feel so sorry for her
I could die'
'Please take care...
of Young-goon.'
'I think I'm feeling...'
'Sym... Sympathy for Young-goon?'
You're saying you feel sympathy?
Please steal Gop-dahn's
sleep flying method.
She has developed
a strange way of flying.
And she flies to Kyu-suk
every night and troubles him.
I'll give you my voice in exchange.
You're listening to me now so you
can tell how beautiful my voice is.
You think your voice
will be enough?
Go on a hunger strike.
Join in the strike, Eun-young.
Steal Eun-young's voice for me.
My flying socks are the second
most important thing to me.
Next to my SK-II cosmetics.
Kyu-suk is mine.
Can you tell me why you are
on a hunger strike?
I think it's my fault.
Please release Young-goon.
Please release her soon.
And you two stay apart!
Everyone.
Do you know why Young-goon
is in the stabilizing room?
She hasn't eaten for
a long time
and is very weak.
So she has to eat under the careful
supervision of the staff.
If she continues to starve
for 3 more days, Young-goon will die.
Do you understand?
I told you taking food through
the nose tube would hurt.
Let's.
How delicious!
Want to eat now without the tube?
She says she doesn't want to eat!
Let me go!
She doesn't want to eat!
Oh, my god! Il-soon!
Il-soon, calm down.
You can't force a patient
without their consent!
She has the right not to eat!
Young-goon!
The vending machine says hi.
Let her go!
She doesn't want to eat.
Let her go.
Are you okay?
I hope you didn't get hurt.
Hold out your hand.
Put them on
Lie on your stomach with your
arms out and rub your feet hard.
It makes static electrical tension
and makes your body float.
You don't eat chicken, right?
I'll start singing for you.
When you start floating,
make yourself small.
I went across the Switzerland
where all the yodelers be.
I tried to run the mountains and they...
I climb up in the mountains
when a clear sunny day
I met a little Swiss girl
in a Swiss chalet.
She taught me how to yodel.
I will teach you how to yodel.
I went across the Switzerland
where all the yodlers be
I tried to run the mountains and they...
I climb up in the mountains
when a clear sunny day.
I met a little Swiss girl
in a Swiss chalet
She taught me how to yodel.
I will teach you how to yodel.
This is the problem!
Look at this face.
It's natural men wouldn't
leave her alone.
You're a cyborg, so you can't eat?
You're a cyborg,
so you don't need to eat?
I'll break down if I eat.
Let's go and eat!
Please, Young-goon?
Come on
Let's eat! Why not?
You're a cyborg but you can
still eat and be OK.
Granny!
Young-goon! My child!
Young-goon!
I didn't use them. I just held
them up to see how they looked.
Your teeth will fall out.
Use them only
when you really miss me.
Look? My teeth all fell out
because of those dentures.
You're lying! You didn't have any
in the first place!
This confounded elastic band!
My back is killing me.
Young-goon, you have to let me go.
Young-goon, my dear!
Granny! Granny!
The purpose of...
What?
The purpose of existence is what?
Granny!
She vanished into a dot.
No being sad.
She was cremated and
her ashes laid to rest.
A week ago.
I thought of you and
brought a spoonful.
It's Granny.
They got mixed up.
Mom.
It's Young-goon!
You didn't tell the people here
you're a mouse, did you?
I mean, a cybor, did you?
You did... didn't you!
How can you think only of yourself?
A person can't just go around
saying everything they want to!
Mom?
Yes?
There's something
I really want to say.
What is it?
Granny's dentures...
You left them behind on purpose,
didn't you?
So she couldn't eat radishes
at the sanatorium.
Oh, woe, woe is me!
Oh woe, woe is me!
Granny, I'm...
I'm in a position where
being sad is forbidden...
No restlessness.
You have no energy because you let
Gop-dahn have all your food!
White rice with...
Plumes of steam coming up from it.
No useless daydreaming
White winter rice...
If a kebab comes along,
pull out the stick and eat it up.
The persimmon spoke.
I'm shy so...
Please take me in one mouthful.
Winter rice.
Granny's pickled radish.
Spring rice.
Summer rice.
Fall rice.
Silent rice.
Holy rice.
All is calm. All is rice.
Round yon virgin mother and child.
Eating noodles, tender and mild.
Her looks are the problem.
Oh, you heartbreaker!
Young-goon?
Young-goon!
It's a rice-megatron.
A device that converts food
calories into electrical energy.
So when you eat rice,
It'll compress and explode it
into energy.
Charging takes a long time.
Food is best when you're in a hurry.
Rice is sufficient for regular
everyday electric energy.
Isn't it incredible?
Here's the door.
They're usually in back.
Really?
Now...
Please remove your top.
What?
I'll have to cut the skin
to open the door.
I'm opening it.
No wonder why.
I get itchy there.
It was because the door was there!
It's open, so I'm putting in
my hand and attaching the device.
Okay.
I'm going in.
Look at all that dust!
I wish I could thank you
for all you've done.
For stealthily stealing
my sympathy before, too.
I'd like to, but...
No thankfulness
I'm forbidden...
by law to feel thankfulness.
What?
Pickled radish!
One, hold the spoon
with your right hand.
Two, take some rice
and bring it to your mouth.
Three, open your mouth
and put the spoon in.
What if I eat,
And the rice-megatron doesn't work?
I'll fix it.
I'm a technician, remember?
Maybe not now, but what if it
breaks down later?
Or after that?
Call me.
I make house calls for repairs.
It's a warranty for life.
PARK Il-soon
Certified Electric Technician
(Rice-megatron Expert)
Warranty for Life
PARK Il-soon
Certified Electric Technician
(Rice-megatron Expert)
Warranty for Life
Warranty for life.
Three, open your mouth
and put the spoon in.
Four, close your mouth and
slowly pull the spoon out.
Five.
We're going to chew.
Chew. Chew.
Are you OK?
Six, swallow.
You can do it, Young-goon.
When I count to five and snap,
you'll swallow.
On five.
Ready?
One
Two
Three
Granny liked listening to the radio.
Me, too. I lose track of time
listening to the radio.
But, she listened to
keep track of time.
Because she was at home all day.
We were listening to the 4:00 show
when mom came home.
With my aunt and uncle.
Young-goon, turn down the radio.
What's that smell?
For crying out loud!
Eating radish all day,
of course it'd stink.
I rest all day and come home to work
with her here like this.
I mean, work all day and
come home to rest.
How could you bear living like this?
Granny likes listening to the radio.
She likes this one even more since...
Her clever little Young-goon
made it for her.
Mom, aunt, uncle! Shut up!
We can't hear the radio.
I said, turn down the radio!
It's giving me a headache.
Come on, the ambulance is waiting.
We should have taken her to
the sanitarium way before!
The purpose of existence is...
Doctor?
The secret of my existence.
I have a secret
I'm not supposed to tell.
Shall I tell you?
The truth is, I'm...
Young-goon.
That tickles.
So you're a cyborg, Young-goon!
It must have been hard for you.
It's okay, now I know.
After knowing, trusting
is the more important thing.
You trust me, right?
But you know what's most important
after knowing and trusting?
Eating. Eating food.
Be?
Me?
Nee?
Nee!
Knee.
Next one.
Da?
A?
Yo, Ra, A?
Da?
- Da?
- Da!
You're a nuke bomb your purpose
zov existence zis...
World zend.
Knee da billion bolts.
You're a nuke bomb.
A nuke bomb?
Purpose of existence zis...
Zis...
Purpose of existence is.
World zend.
Need a billion volts.
Billion volts?
Need a billion volts. Nuke bomb.
What's a zend?
Who's Zend?
Shut up!
Perfect weather, isn't it?
You shouldn't throw trash away
just anywhere.
Why not?
It'll all be over once I blow up.
You're a nuke bomb. Your purpose of
existence is the world's end.
Need a billion volts.
Why would a young lady
like you blow up?
We must carry on living
through thick and thin.
Come on, hurry up!
Think there's really a billion volts
in one bolt of lightning?
Round yon virgin.
Eating noodles.
It's cold.
The persimmon.
The rice.
Have you seen the cork for this?
The person who throws away paper
and gum any place probably lost it.
What's he talking about?
The precious wine got rain in it!
What a waste!
What if it doesn't hit me?
Huh?
Just, give up hope and...
Let's keep our strength up!
What do we do now?
Let's just take off
our wet socks anyway.
But they're not the only things wet.
More than our socks are wet.
www.osdb.link/mkpd