Pavel Lungin Studio
presents
With the financial support of
the Ministry of Culture
of the Russian Federation
OLEG VASILKOV
DMITRY KULICHKOV
AZAMAT NIGMANOV
-== [ www.OpenSubtitles.org ] ==-
Edited by NATALIA KUCHERENKO
Music by ALEXANDER MANOTSKOV
Sound Engineer
VALENTIN BOBROVSKY
Production Designer
KIRILL SHUVALOV
Director of Photography
JANIS EGLITIS
Associate Producer
ANDREY RYDANOV
Producer
PAVEL LUNGIN
Written and Directed by
ALEXEY MIZGIREV
THE CONVOY
Hey, old man, where you going?
What's the matter?
- What'd you do with it?
Hi.
- I said, why throw the bottle?
Why did you smash the bottle?
Call the cops!
He'll kill him!
Jail, old man. You're gonna get
banged up! Cool down!
Tanya!
Does it hurt?
Where?
- Here.
No, not here it doesn't.
The fainting spells will continue
if you keep ignoring the pain.
There's no cure for migraines,
but you do have to control the pain.
Take these with water.
If it hits you, take a bath.
Hot water will stop it for a while.
Stop ignoring the pain, Ignat.
You'll start hallucinating.
Seeing things.
If you keep refusing preventive measures,
I'll report you to the regiment.
I won't.
Comrade Captain, those little brats
wrote a complaint to the precinct
and attached a doctor's note.
You broke this punk's bone,
and messed up his Adam's apple.
The higher-ups are stricter these days.
You know how it is.
Everyone is sick of disorderly conduct.
Were you drunk or something?
- I'm not apologizing.
You're going on detached duty, Ignat,
AWOL retrieval.
Two newbies took off,
and stole cash from the office.
The soldiers aren't armed; fuck 'em.
We're not gonna raise hell.
Who needs that?
But it's government money.
We have to get it back.
I'm assigning you a contract sergeant.
He's waiting for you.
Lay low on detached duty, Ignat.
Wait this out and keep your nose clean.
Understand about the money?
- Yes, sir.
You're going to the AWOL's place of
residence, with a layover in Moscow.
Moscow. Got it.
Don't fuck this up,
Comrade Captain,
one more stunt,
and I'll throw the book at you.
Guaranteed dishonourable
discharge, maybe even worse.
A criminal case.
I'm sick of disorderly conduct.
Permission to speak,
Comrade Captain?
The boys want to know, " Why doesn't
Comrade Captain shave himself?"
They're, like, going on about how
Comrade Captain could cut his throat, like.
"Comrade Captain
can't feel pain".
I think that's bullshit,
Comrade Captain.
I think once you draw blood,
your hand stops by itself.
With a blade, Comrade Captain,
everyone feels pain.
I'm sorry, Comrade Captain.
Good day, Comrade Captain.
They've found Timofeyev, the first AWOL.
The cops are setting up a local raid.
We should go pick him up,
before it's too late.
Should we take guns, Comrade Captain?
What's going on here?
That's what.
- Whatcha waiting for? Call an ambulance.
Stabbed with an awl.
Ran him through, the bastard.
The fucker's hiding up there.
- An athlete, eh?
Timofeyev went nuts,
Comrade Captain.
This is a murder; what can we do?
Let the cops deal with it.
We could use a sniper.
- Nah, not necessary.
Did I get him, Comrade Captain?
With one hit.
A steady arm can come in handy.
Don't get me wrong, Comrade Captain,
I'm not a violent man.
The cop was a piece of shit.
He wouldn't have lived long anyway.
Didn't even know me
and was mouthing off at me.
Started talking about my mother.
That scum tried to humiliate me.
I wasn't having that.
You sure he's dead, Comrade Captain?
Give me the awl, Timofeyev. If the riot
police find out, they'll take you down.
Think I'm a shit?
- You tell me.
I'm not gonna die alone.
You're not gonna kill me.
You think it's not in me?
You take me down, who's gonna
protect you from the cops?
What, like there are no cops in jail?
- You won't live to see remand.
Fine, here it is then.
You stole money. You have to give
it back to the government.
Nineteen thousand.
Spent half of it on grub.
Where's your friend?
- He's not my friend. He's a clown.
Why is he a clown?
- Shrieks like a bird.
And where's he shrieking now?
No way, Comrade Captain.
You really think I'm a shit.
Get in my car now.
I killed a cop. The cops are gonna get me.
In prison, I'm dead either way.
Listen, Captain,
give the money to my mum.
So she can pray for my soul.
- It's the government's money.
You stole it.
I have to sign for it.
It was a good hit, eh?
- No, it wasn't.
You're all fucked. Bitches.
Turned out to be a smart kid.
Saved everyone a lot of hassle.
Nice one, pal.
You saw the kid alive last?
What can you tell me?
- Nothing.
Did he ask you anything?
Hey, bro, did he?
I'm not your bro, pig?
What did you say? Hey!
Hey, come back here.
Get off your high horse, Sergeant.
We identified Timofeyev's body.
I'll sign whatever you want.
If I find out the soldier
didn't jump, I'll come after you.
The boys fight for cash in the barracks,
saving up for demobilization.
A hundred to whoever remains standing.
Timofeyev was the biggest thug.
Stomped one of our boys half to death.
Sent him to the hospital, broke his arm.
Ruptured his spleen, the bastard.
Timofeyev was asking for it.
Don't worry about it, Comrade Captain.
He got what he deserved.
You want a reprimand?
A reprimand? A reprimand would
fuck up my whole contract.
The paymaster would start
getting tight with the money.
No, you don't get it.
Of course I get it.
Eyes on the road.
Can I sit here?
Here, the stool is better.
Hand over the deserter.
- We already did that once.
Unauthorized absence from the unit
means up to four years in prison.
Let's make a deal. The commander
will turn a blind eye.
Tugayev will finish his service
and go home.
I was telling Artyom not to enlist.
But he did anyway.
You got it into his head, fuckwit.
"A boy has a duty..."
Kept saying, "You'll come back a man".
- It was Artyom's decision.
I told him, " Don't enlist.
It's hell. Don't stick your neck
into the noose".
But he did it anyway!
Now look; he's AWOL.
He did the right thing
- The right thing?! What right thing?!
Artyom made his choice.
Why couldn't he choose his mother?
Why? I told him,
"Get a doctor's note".
Didn't I tell him?
That's right, Captain,
Don't look for my son here.
Come here.
What are you doing?
Don't touch that bed.
Just leave my mother alone.
Meat pies?
- With these prices...
...be glad to get those.
- It's good.
Good thing we're leaving tonight.
You'd spend all the
government's cash on grub.
Forget the pies, Comrade Captain.
We have money.
You know, Timofeyev's money.
It's nobody's money.
Don't be afraid of the brass,
Comrade Captain.
They already reported the money
as lost.
They already wrote it off.
We can go out on the town,
burn some cash. Cool, huh?
A whole day in Moscow.
Something to tell the guys about.
You can't do Moscow with no money.
We could see the city,
Comrade Captain; look around.
You like Moscow?
- The city would be mine by nightfall.
When your contract's done,
knock yourself out.
Here, have a pie.
First time in Moscow?
What about you?
- No, not me.
Here.
Nah, that shit does nothing for me.
Moscow is like a whore:
You need a warm-up.
Let me go.
No, nothing I can do.
The boss will look the other way,
I know the secret way to ask.
The captain won't go for it.
I can't go back to the barracks.
I'll go crazy.
No, there's nothing I can do.
Think about it, bro:
Once you jump the fence,
you can't go back, it's hell.
Once you've been AWOL,
you're screwed, you know?
Get off my back.
- What did I say?
A load of crap. The captain's brutal,
he's facing criminal charges.
Drunk and disorderly?
- Murder, but not proved yet.
Premeditated murder?
The boys say he killed his daughter.
His own daughter?
He'll get you too, bro.
Let me go, bro.
Don't push me. I'll get mad.
Go ahead
- Yeah? I could, y'know...
Whatever. It's just...
- Just what?
Just, you don't have the balls.
- I can leave.
Again, huh?
- What?
You're scared again.
- I'm not scared.
Thought I was wasted, right?
Thought I was nice?
Lay off, you'll get yourself dirty.
- Thought I'd take pity on you?
Don't touch shit, you'll stink.
Jail doesn't do shit for your kind.
People like you should be killed.
I swear, the captain'll turn a blind eye,
I know a secret.
Damn Moscow!
It's not working, Comrade Captain?
Give me your hands.
Take them off.
Why, Comrade Captain?
The cops will sniff around.
Down. Pushups.
- What do you mean, down?
You don't get it.
- What, in a public toilet?
- You mean, hands on the ground?
No, you don't get it.
One, two, three,
four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine,
ten, eleven...
You hurt yourself?
- No, Comrade Captain.
It's the pies. Bad for my stomach.
- Did you know that before?
Yeah.
- Then why'd you stuff your face?
It hurts. I need a doctor.
What the hell?
- Good ketchup.
You'll have to lick it up.
Get up.
What's with you?
What about him?
- Eyes front.
What's this?
Ketchup, Comrade Captain.
Disgusting shit.
You're disgusting shit.
Need proof?
Permission to clean myself up,
Comrade Captain?
Forward march.
You got eyes like a bull,
Comrade Captain.
Don't red flies bother you?
Why didn't you tell me
the sergeant attacked you?
He didn't.
Tanya!
Tanya...
I told you, he's a goner.
I'm watching you, bitch.
Why didn't you run away?
Give me your hands.
What's this concerning,
Comrade Captain?
I need to file a report.
Absence without leave.
Don't report the sergeant. They'll
hold you responsible for the money.
They'll fuck you up, for sure.
I never touched the money,
and I'm still getting screwed.
Imagine, the two of us in the same cell,
Comrade Captain, like brothers.
What money, Comrade Captain?
I'm hungry.
Why didn't you run?
- Didn't have the time. That's it.
Damn sergeant spends everything on grub.
I could, too.
You chickened out.
No, I told you, I wanted to run
but missed my chance.
My mother always said, " Tell a good
joke, and the hunger will go away".
What do you think,
Comrade Captain, will it go away?
What do you think?
Wanna hear a joke about meat pies?
Shut up.
Come to pick a fight?
Do you serve friendly forces?
Always.
A thousand roubles.
A grand for half a litre?
Do you drink?
- No.
I see.
- What do you see?
Look at this nick. Container damage,
can't sell it anyway.
The neck's chipped...
Here, take it.
That shit does nothing for me.
- It's good vodka, premium stuff.
We've got no money.
- It's a gift.
I really need your help.
Things are hard right now.
What am I, stupid?
I need nineteen thousand,
that's nothing for Moscow.
Go to the darkies working in the city.
They've got cash, not me.
I don't work stalls.
I'm a salaried employee.
So you won't help out?
- I have no money. None!
You want me to give you my word?
- I don't need your word.
What do you need?
- You got a problem with me?
No, I'm simply telling you to fuck off.
- Wanna hear a joke about friendship?
Two old friends run into each other.
One says, "How've you been?"
"Not bad. You?"
He goes, "I'm gay now".
Heard this one before?
- No.
So the other one asks,
"Do you have a car?"
"No". "What about an apartment?"
"No".
"What about money in the bank?"
"No money either".
"You know what", the other one says.
"As one friend to another, you're
not gay, you're just a cocksucker".
Ignat.
Is that your wife?
One husband sent his wife a telegram
that just said "Tenroubleme".
Need money?
I'm Issa. What's your name?
Which bus are you waiting for?
What are you, mute?
Don't know where you're going?
Out-of-towner?
Need money?
I can show you where you
can get hold of some money.
Eat up, friend.
The food is good here.
What are you, squeamish?
Should I be?
I'm sorry, friend,
I can see you're angry at me.
You don't know what I'm talking
about. Let me explain.
Can't get my head on straight.
This one whore has fried my brain.
Can't get my shit together.
I live like a zombie.
Drink, friend, eat.
I bought her an apartment,
but that wasn't enough for her.
Wants her own business.
I work as a foreman here.
The money isn't bad, of course,
but nowhere near enough.
My wife is sick
and I gotta help out my two brothers.
She doesn't give a shit.
Listen, if you're not going to drink
then at least have some food.
Good-looking bitch.
Looks as good coming
as she does going.
But I can't afford her.
Can't leave her.
But where am I supposed to get
the money? Help me out, Captain.
What are you waiting for?
It's the cops.
- Let them in.
They're cops.
- I heard you. Let them in.
The cops?
- Let them in.
Are you Issa?
- Come to have a plate of fish soup?
You can joke around later, smart ass.
How many heads in here... seventy?
Exactly, buddy. Fifty-seven.
Registration, employment quota,
everything is in order.
The going rate is one grand per Tajik.
- Can't you give me a discount?
What are you grinning at?
- Why so rude, buddy?
If you don't pay up,
you're coming with us.
Eat up, friend.
The food is good here.
This is not my day.
What's your name?
- Tamara.
From Chechnya?
Russian.
What does your husband call you?
- Tamara.
What about, like, a pet name?
Show me your passport.
Why so quiet, Tamara?
What about you?
- What about me?
You had the soup, right?
Now go help out the cook.
Help out how?
- Start screaming: "Suck my cock, pigs".
The cops won't touch a kid,
and they'll let the woman go.
What's the matter?
Got no balls?
Go get in the car.
- Why?
Get in the car.
Please don't.
- Don't what?
Please.
- Please what?
I'm begging you.
We'll just talk.
I wanted another helping.
Having fun?
I'm sorry.
Sorry about what?
I apologize.
Apologize for what?
Sorry.
What's with this "sorry, sorry..." crap?
I'm sorry. For everything.
- What are you, stupid?
Get lost.
Who are you?
The cook.
Where's the plate?
Here, have some.
Doesn't it hurt?
- What?
Your hand.
- No, it doesn't hurt here.
Don't do this, bro.
Come on man, don't be suicidal.
You're not my bro, pig.
What did you say?
I'm not paying.
Watch it, Issa. If we find Chechens
here, prices will double.
You shouldn't have come, Sergeant.
There won't be any money.
Help me out, Captain.
Cut the bitch's face up.
I don't care if her face is fucked up,
as long as she's put in her place.
Are we paid up for the soup?
- Hey, what are you talking about.
Relax, we're all good.
You're a stranger in Moscow.
In and out,
do your thing and disappear.
Help some people, make some money.
How much money do you want, Captain?
Don't be shy.
Deal? Eh, friend?
You shouldn't have got involved,
Comrade Captain.
The cops looked mean.
Bloodshot eyes, like bulls.
My mother always says,
"Smile when they're messing with you".
Comrade Captain, you shouldn't
have got into it.
Could've turned ugly.
Did you like the soup?
- Smells like piss.
You're right, Captain,
people around here are mean.
They insult us,
throw a punch for no reason.
It's hard, being on your own here.
We should be throwing punches, not them.
Stick together, to take what's ours.
What's yours around here?
- I'll show you, OK?
Have we left Moscow yet?
Almost.
Do you have a woman?
- No.
Never had one?
- I did.
And now?
- No.
If you want I can be your woman.
OK.
You don't care?
- Well, no.
You're lying.
I can see that you care.
No, I'm not lying.
Bitch.
He'll be back with his brothers.
Your husband?
- My landlord.
Nice place.
- I earned it.
You are a bitch.
I earned this place.
You do the math.
One hour with a prostitute
costs two hundred bucks.
Issa comes over for two hours
every other day.
Do the math.
That adds up to seventy thousand a year.
In three years, I've more than
paid this place off.
Help me, please?
Tell Issa you're my husband.
Issa's not Russian. He can get nasty.
He'll jump on you.
They'll lock him up.
Then we'll trade him the criminal
case for the apartment.
Nineteen thousand.
Dollars?
Nineteen thousand roubles.
For nineteen grand,
you also have to punch his face in.
Are you going to fight him?
Comrade Captain, I can talk to him.
I swear, we'll make friends with him.
Wanna hear a joke about a fight?
Tell your jokes to fools.
Leave me alone.
You're about to get caught up
in something horrible.
You killed your daughter -
enough already!
Having a laugh?
No, Comrade Captain.
Trying to get you to have a laugh.
It's not working.
I know. I'm not funny.
Being funny - that's victory.
You make someone laugh,
and he's yours forever.
He'll do whatever you want.
No need to raise your fists.
You feel sorry for yourself,
but you're scared of admitting it.
It's always like that with guilt.
That's why you terrorize everyone.
Get angry, dish out abuse.
A real bull.
Why didn't you make a run for it
at the train station?
I felt sorry for you.
Admit it: You didn't have the balls.
You're a real bull, Comrade Captain.
I always feel sorry for people like that.
Listen here.
It wasn't my fault, you hear me?
Tanya was little.
She got a stomach ache.
My wife was away on business,
and I was late for my watch.
I asked her, "Want to go to the hospital?"
She didn't answer. No reaction.
I thought, must be food poisoning.
Gave her some emetic to make her vomit.
Still nothing. No reaction.
I said, " Speak up. I have to go
to the unit. I'm on watch.
If it's food poisoning, go puke,
or go sit on the toilet".
Again, no reaction.
She just stared at me silently.
So I lost it. Yes, I did.
Hit her with my hand, just a little.
Again, no reaction -
just stared at me silently.
So I spat and left.
Told her, " You can die,
for all I care".
Tanya...
What's the matter with you?
- Your turn: Caw!
You're a cock.
- I'm not a cock, Comrade Captain.
I'm a raven.
Cocks go looking for a fight.
Ravens are the opposite.
People eat cocks.
Ravens eat people.
Ravens live forever.
Cocks die.
Ravens protect people.
When he finds a suffering man,
he takes the suffering from him.
Do the pills help?
- Yes.
It wasn't my fault.
What am I, a doctor
to know the difference between
diarrhea and acute appendicitis?
Throw this away,
and you'll forget everything.
Throw the rock, Comrade Captain
and your pain will go away.
I was just messing around,
Comrade Captain.
Wanted to get back at you, like guys
do, when they're pushed too far.
Didn't work out for me,
I just punished myself.
The cops tricked me,
Comrade Captain.
Took the money.
Tore my fatigues.
Well, I got a hooker
at the intersection.
Paid off the pimp, hailed a car.
The cops stopped the car and were like,
"The broad doesn't have papers, pay up".
Like I don't know they get
kickbacks from every whore.
So I told the pigs to go suck it.
They started beating me up,
arrested me.
I had to give them all the money,
or I'd get done for disorderly conduct.
What are you staring at,
Comrade Captain?
Want to punish me? Go ahead,
I'm right here.
How much did the cops take?
- All of it. Nineteen thousand.
They're getting kickbacks
from the intersection.
A sergeant was in here earlier,
you made him pay nineteen thousand.
That money belongs to me,
give it back.
Where's my money? Hey!
- I know nothing about it. New shift.
Give me your commanding officer's
phone number.
No way, bro.
- I'm not your bro, pig.
I swear, our boys didn't take any money.
- Swear man to man?
Sure, whatever you want.
You don't understand.
Let's see your ID, Captain.
No, you don't get it.
I said, let's see your papers.
Stand up.
Here! Give me back my money.
How can you know which are yours?
Mine is signed.
Enough, don't kill him.
Should I get a cell ready?
So, are we bros now?
Give me back my money.
Should we lock him up?
- Nah, call the army patrol.
Comrade Captain?
- Let his people deal with him.
They're on-duty police officers,
and you, Comrade Captain,
start throwing chairs around.
Demanding money.
This is extortion, plain and simple.
This isn't self-defense.
I'm not apologizing.
You have the AWOL?
It says here: " Two soldiers
accompanied by an officer".
These are my detached duty documents.
I know all about these trips.
Been on them myself.
Too late to get the AWOL
back quietly, bro.
You have tickets for
Timofeyev and Tugayev.
Timofeyev is listed in
a murder case.
Tugayev is wanted
as a deserter and an accessory.
You know where he is?
Tugayev is wanted throughout the district.
Murder of a police officer.
You realize who you're transporting?
If it were up to me
I'd bulldoze this entire place.
I'd get the equipment and raze
the entire place to the ground.
Bury everyone under the asphalt.
Go back to your detached duty, Comrade
Captain, but give it some thought.
If you don't take care of this,
I swear on my insignia, you'll be sorry.
The cops fucked you over,
Comrade Captain, didn't they?
Timofeyev should've been raising hell
here instead of the barracks.
Wanna hear a joke about barracks?
Do you visit the grave?
- No.
Everything's fine with you then?
I'm not apologizing.
Take as much as you need.
- It's OK.
You need it.
You should move here.
I can't handle Moscow.
My husband will help you out.
If I can find work, I'll risk it.
No, you won't come.
Ignat.
It wasn't your fault.
- I know.
It wasn't your fault, Ignat.
It wasn't your fault.
I see her,
when the pain gets too much.
I know I'm hallucinating.
I see Tanya, alive and well.
I don't take the pills.
I don't resign.
I'm scared to change things.
Scared to change anything, you know?
You should move here.
You should.
Forget the money.
Tanya is dead.
You have to go on living.
You don't understand.
You should've taken the money,
it was a heartfelt offer.
You wanted to run? Go ahead.
What are you doing, Comrade Captain?
They'll fuck us for this.
- I'm not apologizing.
I told you he'd let me go.
I know a secret.
Thank you, Comrade Captain.
You shouldn't have. He's a piece of shit.
- And you're any better?
You wanted to see the city?
Go ahead. Forward march.
Want some, Comrade Captain?
- Where did you get it?
I got it to warm up the whore.
A hundred and seventy roubles.
Three stars.
Probably counterfeit
- It's not counterfeit. What do you mean?
Definitely counterfeit.
Why would you say that, Comrade Captain?
Say what?
Where did you put the bottle?
The Captain changed his mind?
No, it's just me.
You like money?
- Nah, I want to help the captain.
Get out.
Nineteen thousand, as promised?
I'm not gonna sleep with you.
- You don't have to.
I like you.
No, go away.
I swear, we'll become friends.
I know a secret.
I'll deal with Issa, I'm telling you.
- Enough, clown, forget it.
It stinks here, Comrade Captain,
like our unit depot.
Here, friend, buy some fresh pork.
Your stomach will thank you.
How much for a kilo?
- Three-fifty per kilo. Good price.
This place is nuts, Comrade Captain.
Bet it tastes like asbestos.
It's a boar. Good meat.
How are sales?
Today's been slow. Too cold.
Have you made nineteen thousand?
Got money?
Just take the meat; consider it a gift.
You don't have to pay.
What, got too much cash?
Say something.
- What should I say?
Say, "Caw".
Say, "Caw, caw".
To ward off evil. I'm the evil.
I have the money, Captain.
Listen, that's not enough.
Right, take it.
Shut up, bitch.
I said, shut up!
Who are you?
- The husband.
Whose husband?
Bring some soup; your husband is home.
You know
who you're dealing with, bitch?
Issa, I paid off that apartment.
I'm going to live by myself now.
You're a whore.
Wanna hear a joke about a prostitute?
Two friends run into each other.
The first one says, "How've you been?"
"Not bad. What about you?"
She goes, "I became a prostitute".
Heard this one before?
- No.
The other one says,
"Do you have a car?"
"No." "What about an apartment?" "No".
"What about money in the bank?"
"No money either".
"You know what", says her friend,
"Let me tell you a secret.
You're no prostitute.
You're a whore".
Bitch.
Now you.
Tear him a new one.
Take his papers.
He's a nobody. Go right ahead.
You fucked him?
- What am I, an idiot?
No, you're a whore.
He was joking.
Cut that bitch a smile?
- No, you do it.
Got no balls?
- She's your whore. You cut her.
Please, baby, don't.
Move your hands, bitch.
Please, baby, have mercy.
You're dead, bitch. Dead.
Please, Issa.
She's nothing but an animal.
You go right ahead.
You think I'm disgusting, don't you?
Cut her a smile.
Is this funny?
Go ahead, laugh.
Thank you, baby, thank you, Issa.
What's with you, clown?
You're a cock.
You look like one. Rooster, right?
Caw.
He's a cocksucker, bro.
Cottonball is on duty tonight.
Let's call Cottonball.
Want to organize a little
gangbang for the kid?
That's what Issa wants.
Are you going to fuck him yourself?
I didn't sign up for this shit.
You people from the Caucuses...
To hear you talk, you're so cool.
But it's all talk.
What's your problem, Cottonball?
You know why they call me Cottonball?
Because I'm soft.
Want some, buddy?
- That shit does nothing for me.
Don't worry, kid, I'll sneak you out
through the basement.
What business brought you here?
Don't worry about it.
Why are you here?
- Unauthorized absence from the unit.
Fuck those bitches.
Nah, I enlisted myself.
- Why would you do that?
Don't worry about it.
- No, why did you enlist?
My father told me, when he was
demobilized he thanked the army.
I wanted to thank it too.
And did you?
Private Timofeyev, we're from
the same town. They started...
messing with him at the barracks.
They were just testing him.
But Timofeyev figured it was a matter
of principle. Fought back.
Timofeyev was a vicious one
- a real bull.
He used to say, when he was mad,
he couldn't see anything.
Nothing but red flies.
I always feel bad for a kid
when they break him.
The sergeants humiliated Timofeyev,
so he went AWOL.
I jumped the fence with him.
Figured, since we were friends,
I'd convince him to come back.
Worst case, they'd beat us up,
but probably even let us off
so they could meet their
statistical targets.
Timofeyev wouldn't listen to me.
Now he's dead.
Now I have to pay for the both of us.
They tell me I could get six years.
Fuck those bitches.
Nah, man, army life is great
I swear, want me to cross myself?
You know how to suck cock?
You know what this means?
It's a violin.
No, not a violin. A fiddle.
You know?
- So it's a violin. So what?
In prison, it means you know
how to suck cock.
Want me to bring my wife later?
She's always understanding.
Always up for anything.
May I sit next to you?
You don't have to.
- Please?
You won't be sorry, I promise.
I told you, you don't have the balls
to make a run for it.
You'll lose your nerve.
- Didn't want the ticket to go to waste.
The ticket is bought and paid for.
I have to go.
Good math, kid:
Second desertion
more than doubles your sentence.
It's all shit, eh?
Is it time, Comrade Captain?
Is our train departing?
We have to go, Comrade Captain.
It's all shit.
Just take it, Comrade Captain.
It's a gift.
From the bottom of the heart.
It's not counterfeit. Real liquor.
Honest-to-goodness vodka.
That's right.
Want some?
- Yes.
I'll come back here on my holidays,
they'll be sorry they were ever born.
This shit does nothing for me.
He was begging, saying,
"Please, I really need it".
Offered me his wife as reward.
Says, "You won't be sorry, no way".
So, OK, what do I care?
OK what?
- Who? Issa?
I thought I'd make some money,
nineteen thousand.
I know I'm not funny,
Comrade Captain. You're right.
It's all shit, Comrade Captain.
I don't want any.
What's with you?
- I don't want any more.
I said, drink.
- What's the matter, Comrade Captain?
What?
- I don't want any more, period.
Where did you get the vodka?
- From some Siberians at the train station.
Don't expect a reward for going AWOL.
I'll personally report you as a deserter.
You're under contract.
Don't expect leniency.
It'll be a criminal case.
- I'm sorry, Comrade Captain.
You don't understand.
I only spent some of it. Thought
I'd keep the rest for vacation.
Promise me, Comrade Captain,
that you won't report me.
It's nobody's money.
That's why I took it.
If you found it on the ground,
you'd take it too.
Why raise a stink?
If you hadn't seen the vodka,
you'd never have guessed.
I chose to confess, and handed
over the money voluntarily.
Full confession, Comrade Captain.
Let's just call it that.
Drink, bitch.
I'll finish it.
Nineteen thousand,
minus liquor and cigarettes.
Where's the rest?
Are you holding out?
I can put some money in
if necessary.
Write up the nineteen thousand
at the accounting office.
How much did they take?
- You can take the money.
We already wrote it off. That's not
the issue: First, AWOL, theft,
a dead police officer; suicide...
What did you do to make that soldier jump?
- How much money do I have to add?
Write up Private Tugayev, Comrade Captain.
Officially, at the garrison.
We'll start an investigation,
file a case. He's going to jail.
Everyone is sick of disorderly conduct.
What do you want?
I request that you let the AWOL go.
The kid won't survive military jail.
- Why not?
Shrieks like a bird.
Too late.
Wanna hear a joke
about a cat and mouse?
OK.
A cat goes hunting in the basement.
Walks in, sees a pair of huge eyes.
He gets scared and goes, "Who are you?"
"A mouse".
"Why do you have such huge eyes?"
- "I'm shitting".
What do you want?
Not funny, huh?
- Nah, it's OK.
Let the AWOL go, bro.
He'll die in jail.
I can't.
- Why not?
Too late, bro. Can't do it.
Why not?
Everyone is sick of disorderly conduct.
It's time, Comrade Captain.
We're on a schedule.
Five minutes.
Where does it hurt?
It hurts here.
- No, it doesn't hurt there.
Don't let them take me right away,
Comrade Captain.
Let me stay here a while.
You know where it hurts, kid?
Where?
- Nowhere.
Soon, Comrade Captain?
Don't let them take me right away,
Comrade Captain.
I don't need this.
What's so special about him?
What have I done, Comrade Captain?
Stand up! Atten-hut!
Forward march!
I feel bad for the kid.
Though he was a complete idiot.
I could tell right away.
What now, Comrade Captain?
Back to the unit, eh?
Give the government's money back,
sign for it, right?
What time is lunch, Comrade Captain?
Is it time yet?
Please forgive me, Comrade Captain.
Please don't.
You want to punish me? Go ahead,
just don't put me in jail.
Comrade Captain, please forgive me.
Comrade Captain, please don't.
Please forgive me, Comrade Captain.
Comrade Captain...
Thank you.
Thank you, Comrade Captain.
Just don't put me in jail.
Promise me, Comrade Captain.
I have your word, yeah?
Written and directed by
ALEXEY MIZGIREV
Produced by
PAVEL LUNGIN
Director of Photography
JANIS EGLITIS
Production Designer
KIRILL SHUVALOV
Music by
ALEXANDER MANOTSKOV
Ignat
OLEG VASILKOV
Artyom
AZAMAT NIGMANOV
Sergeant
DMITRY KULICHKOV
Tamara
RUSLANA DORONINA
Issa
IVAN AKHADI
Ignat's Wife
DANIELA STOYANOVICH
Timofeyev
EVGENY ANTROPOV
Cottonball
TARAS KOLYADOV
Preuzeto sa www.titlovi.com
;  www.OpenSubtitles.org